https://www.threadcheck.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Our website uses cookies!
By continuing to use our website you agree with our use of cookies in accordance with our Privacy Policy. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings.
OK
Search
Search
Home
Categories
Thread GagesUnified Inch Thread GagesUnified Metric Thread GagesNational Pipe Thread GagesBritish Thread GagesAcme Thread GagesAPI GagesProfile GagesFlexible Hole Location GagesUnified Miniature Screw Thread GagesPg Conduit Thread Gages per Din 40431Thread Check Software3 Wire Thread Measuring SystemStandard Holders and WiresMetric Holders with WiresMetric Holders less WiresStandard Holders less WiresAcme Holders and WiresAcme Holders less Wires3-Wire Thread Measuring Holder Library SetsThread & Gear Measuring WiresThread Measuring WiresGear Measuring WiresTri-Roll Thread Comparator SystemsDigital Thread Depth GagesPower Driven Thread GagingThreading ToolsTaps, Dies Cutting ToolsTap and Die Box SetsSpecial Threading DiesCheck List Aid to Good TappingRake Angle Versus MaterialTap Drill SizesSpecial TapsSelf Locking ThreadThread Cutting TermsCarbide Thread MillsRecommended TapsThread FormsTapping Faults and Causes ChartHand Tap ChamfersCarbide Taps / MSDSCylindrical Gaging ProductsCylindrical Ring GagesSnap GagesMaster Setting DiscsCylindrical Taper GagesClass ZZ Pin Gages – Sets and LibrariesClass Z and X Pin Gages - Sets and LibrariesStandard Class X Plug Gage Assemblies - Steel - InchesStandard Class X Plug Gage Members - Steel - InchesReversible Plain Plug Gages - Class XX - ZZReversible Plain Plug Gages - Class XXXReversible Plain Plug Gages - Micro SizeTaperlock Plain Plug Gages - Class XX - ZZTrilock Plain Plug Gages - Class XX - ZZHex Plug GagesProgressive Cylindrical Plug GagesHexalobe GagesSurveillance MastersMicrometer Set Masters - Model 16-1/2 up to 6.0"/150mmMicrometer Set Masters - Model 16-1 up to 6.0"/150mmMicrometer Set Masters - Model 112 up to 12"/300mmMicrometer Set Masters - Model 01-1 up to 1.0"/25.0mmDepth Micrometer Masters - Model ADMDepth Micrometer Masters - Model DMVernier Caliper MastersQUICKCHEKZ Axis CheckMeasuring InstrumentsStarrett Hand ToolsINSIZE Measuring InstrumentsChamfer GageBalax Taps and GagesBarcor GagesGagemaker Thread Measuring InstrumentsTDWIN Taper SoftwareMahr® Inc. GagesMitutoyo Measuring ToolsPhase II+ Measuring ToolsGagemaker Thread GagesFeeler GaugesAssortment Packs – Style APFeeler Gauge – Carbon Steel - Metric - Style MFBFeeler Gauge Coils – High Carbon Steel - Style FCFeeler Gauge Coils – Stainless Steel - Style FCFeeler Gauge High Carbon Steel Blades - Style FBFeeler Gauge Stainless Steel Blades– Style FBFeeler Gauges – Carbon Steel - Metric - Style MFCFeeler Heavy Thickness Gauges - Carbon Steel – Style FBInch Feeler Gauge SetsMetric Feeler Gauge SetsMetric Taper GaugesShim Stock - Stainless Steel – Style SHSpline GaugesCalibration ServicesHardness Testing EquipmentKnoop Hardness TestingRockwell Hardness TestingMitutoyo Hardness TestingSPI Hardness TestingBrinell Hardness TestingDurometersHardness Test BlocksHardness Testing AccessoriesHardness Testing File SetsImpact Hardness TestingIndentersKing Hardness TestingVickers Hardness TestingIndustrial PublicationsMachineryMaterialsArchitecture / DesignConstructionCNCEn EspanolMaintenance / ReliabilityWeldingCD-Rom / SoftwareComputer GraphicsElectricalEngineeringManufacturingMeasuringMachinery’s HandbooksProduction Machining ServicesIndustrial Safety Supply
ServicesTechnical InfoBlogContact
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
WHAT THIS POLICY COVERS
This policy covers personal information that we receive when you use the threadcheck.com website. “Personal information” is information that can be linked to you as an individual, such as your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number. By visiting and using threadcheck.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
INFORMATION YOU KNOWINGLY GIVE TO US
We receive and may store any personal information you actively send us or enter on our website. You provide such information when you fill out a contact or lead form, request a free trial or send us e-mails.
INFORMATION THAT IS AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED BY OUR SYSTEM
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through the internet. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to allow our system to recognize your browser and to provide you certain browsing conveniences. You can configure your browser to reject cookies, but if you do so, you might not be able to experience all the functionality and conveniences of our website.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of threadcheck.com. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they visited prior to coming to this website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to maintain and improve the website’s technical performance. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of service, available at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html, and the Google Privacy Policy, available at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser. Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by “anonymizeIp” to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so-called IP masking). In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA.
WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use the personal information that we receive to operate the website and to fit your needs and demands for using our products and services. We do not rent or sell your personal information to any entity. We do not share your personal information with any entity, except when:
We have your permission; or
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes; or when we must exercise our legal rights, protect our property, defend against legal claims, or otherwise comply with the law; or
We believe it is appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, threats to personal safety, or violation of this website's terms of use.
Threadcheck.com may at times contact you at your email address to keep you informed about the latest news or developments. Should you not want to receive such communications, you will find details about how to opt out the first time you are contacted.
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY
The only people, who have access to personal information collected on this web site, either directly, or through use of Google Analytics, are employees and our marketing agency who have a need to know and who are bound by nondisclosure agreements and this privacy policy. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the personal information that we store. Please note that the threadcheck.com website may contain links to third party websites. These third party websites may send their own cookies to collect data and solicit personal information. Therefore, we cannot guarantee your privacy when visiting such third party sites, nor the accuracy or acceptability of any services provided by such third parties.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may update this policy from time to time. When any significant changes are made to this policy, we will post a notification in a prominent place on this web site so that you may be made aware of the changes.
This notification will appear the first time you log on to this website following a significant change in this policy.
EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This policy is effective as of May 29th 2018.
